hackerexperience.com 2016-03-12

# Privacy Policy

###### Hacker Experience Privacy Policy

Privacy is top priority at Hacker Experience, and we like to explain our Privacy Policy in clear and simple words:
* Personal information you provide us

\- Your email. We keep them for verification purposes.
\- If you login using Facebook or Twitter social plugin, we have access to your social ID, username and email. We keep your social ID and email for verification purposes.

* We collect

\- Browser family
\- Operating system
\- IP address
\- Referrer website

All these information provides us better information as to where our users are having trouble accessing, in which parts of the world the page is taking too long to load, or how their gaming experience is. 

* We use

\- Piwik - [Piwik](http://piwik.org/) is an _open source_ web analytics platform that respects it's users privacy. 
\- New Relic - New Relic provides better statistics regarding page load and application aspects. No personal-identifying information is collected.
\- Cookies - We use cookies to enable a more personal experience on the game. We do not track other sites than hackerexperience.com. Hacker Experience might not work without cookies.
\- Google Adsense - Google Ads help keep Hacker Experience free.

* We protect

\- Your data - We do not rent or sell your personal/identifying data, nor make it public. It is safely stored on a private, access-limited server.
\- Your password - Your password is uniquely salted using a slow hashing function.
\- Your email - We do not spam.

* When purchasing premium membership

\- We do not store your credit card information.
\- We use SSL and encrypt your data from our site to the payment gateway.

* We use Google AdSense, that

\- Uses cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to Hacker Experience.
\- Uses DoubleClick*, a cookie that enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your previous accesses to other sites on the Internet.

*Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

* Please note

\- The use of the site constites your full acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with it, please refrain from using www.hackerexperience.com and all related domains.
\- We may change our privacy policy from time to time. Although efforts will be made to announce any changes on the Forum Announcements Board, we may do so in our sole discretion. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. Therefore, we encourage you to visit this page regularly.
**You can opt out of our tracking analytics at any time using the checkbox below**

**We use, follow and recommend the ACM code of ethics**  
<http://www.acm.org/about/code-of-ethics>

This Term of Service was first published on 30/08/2014 and last revised on 30/08/2014.
